<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Attending on IEEE Haptics Symposium 2024</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/attending/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Attending on IEEE Haptics Symposium 2024</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>IEEE Haptics Symposium 2024. Theme adapted from Netlify CMS.</copyright>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/attending/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/attending/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/attending/registration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;registration&#34;&gt;Registration&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are excited to welcome the worldwide haptics community to Long Beach, CA for the 2024 Haptics Symposium! Registration is now open through the &lt;a href=&#34;https://web.cvent.com/event/11d034c1-348e-426f-967d-af0024f9415d/summary&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;registration site&lt;/a&gt;. Early bird deadline for registration is February 23, 2024. For a preferred hotel rate at the conference hotel, use the &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hilton.com/en/book/reservation/rooms/?ctyhocn=LGBMYDT&amp;amp;arrivalDate=2024-04-06&amp;amp;departureDate=2024-04-11&amp;amp;groupCode=CDT90H&amp;amp;room1NumAdults=1&amp;amp;cid=OM%2CWW%2CHILTONLINK%2CEN%2CDirectLink&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hotel Maya&lt;/a&gt; link here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please read the following &lt;strong&gt;before&lt;/strong&gt; you begin the registration process:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;conference-registration-will-require-the-following&#34;&gt;Conference registration will require the following:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;IEEE account username and password&lt;/em&gt;, as appropriate. Your user credentials will be used to verify IEEE membership and eligibility for discounted IEEE member rates during the registration process. If you do not have your user credentials, please follow the instructions listed under the FAQs tab on the registration page to recover your IEEE username and password.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Registration discount code&lt;/em&gt;, as appropriate. IEEE member rates apply to both IEEE members and IEEE Technical Committee on Haptics (TCH) members. TCH members who are not also IEEE members should obtain a discount code prior to completing their online registration in order to obtain IEEE member rates. All requests for discount codes should be submitted via email to the Haptics Symposium Registration Chair (&lt;a href=&#34;mailto:registration@hapticssymposium.org&#34;&gt;registration@hapticssymposium.org&lt;/a&gt;) with the subject HAPTICS TCH Discount Code Request. Requests should include the registrant&amp;rsquo;s name and the type of discount code being requested.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Titles of the accepted&lt;/em&gt; short papers, technical papers, work-in-progress papers, hands-on demonstrations, and/or cross-cutting challenges that you will be presenting. All accepted papers, posters, demos, and cross-cutting challenges must be presented in person.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Payment of extra page charges&lt;/em&gt;, as appropriate. If the camera-ready version of your technical paper exceeds six pages, you will be charged $200 for each additional page, up to two pages. Failure to pay the additional page fees will prevent the publication of your paper in the archival IEEE conference proceedings.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;conference-registration-includes&#34;&gt;Conference Registration includes:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Attendance at all Haptics Symposium activities, including cross-cutting challenges, podium presentations, poster presentations, hands-on demonstrations, and exhibits.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Access to various mentoring activities such as resume database, WIP mentoring, and early investigator lunch. Sign up for these activities on the &lt;a href=&#34;../mentoring/&#34;&gt;mentoring page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The electronic conference program and proceedings.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Wireless internet access for the duration of the conference.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Coffee breaks on all four days of the conference.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Welcome reception on Sunday, April 7, 2024.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;One ticket for the banquet on Tuesday, April 9, 2024.  If available, additional banquet tickets may be offered for purchase during registration.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;one-day-registration-includes&#34;&gt;One-day Registration includes:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Attendance at a single day of the conference (April 7, 8, 9, or 10). You will need to specify which day you choose to attend prior to your arrival.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;One-day registration includes participation in the evening event (i.e., opening reception, or WIP poster session, etc.) taking place on your chosen day. Due to the high cost of attendance, registration on April 9 does not include a banquet ticket. Anyone purchasing a one-day registration is welcome to purchase a banquet ticket(s), regardless of the day of attendance. There is no evening event on the last day of the conference.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Access to various mentoring activities such as resume database, WIP mentoring, and early investigator lunch. Sign up for these activities on the &lt;a href=&#34;../mentoring/&#34;&gt;mentoring page&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The electronic conference program and proceedings.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Wireless internet access for the day you attend.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Coffee breaks for the day of attendance.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;registration-changes&#34;&gt;Registration Changes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Any changes to your registration can be made by revisiting the registration page and making the desired modifications. To make changes, you will need the confirmation number provided in your registration confirmation email.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mentoring Activities</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/attending/mentoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/attending/mentoring/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;mentoring-activities&#34;&gt;Mentoring Activities&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Haptics Symposium conference acknowledges the valuable role of mentoring in the personal and professional development of students and researchers in the haptics community. We are committed to providing mentorship opportunities for this year’s conference attendees. To that end, we have created the following programs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;resume-database&#34;&gt;Resume Database&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have created a database of resumes for people seeking career opportunities in academia or industry. This database can be accessed by our industry sponsors and members who have open job offerings. The database is created and shared before the conference. The conference will not keep the resumes after the completion of the conference.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Venue Information</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/attending/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/attending/venue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;venue-information&#34;&gt;Venue Information&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The IEEE Haptics Symposium 2024 will be held at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hilton.com/en/book/reservation/rooms/?ctyhocn=LGBMYDT&amp;amp;arrivalDate=2024-04-06&amp;amp;departureDate=2024-04-11&amp;amp;groupCode=CDT90H&amp;amp;room1NumAdults=1&amp;amp;cid=OM%2CWW%2CHILTONLINK%2CEN%2CDirectLink&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hotel Maya - a DoubleTree by Hilton&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; in Long Beach, CA, USA.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;//localhost:1313/img/2024maya.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For greatest convenience, and to secure all the meeting rooms needed for the conference,  it is essential that all attendees book their hotel rooms at the conference hotel. We have secured a competitive rate of $269 per night, with complimentary Internet access, and the hotel rooms are lovely. &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hilton.com/en/book/reservation/rooms/?ctyhocn=LGBMYDT&amp;amp;arrivalDate=2024-04-06&amp;amp;departureDate=2024-04-11&amp;amp;groupCode=CDT90H&amp;amp;room1NumAdults=1&amp;amp;cid=OM%2CWW%2CHILTONLINK%2CEN%2CDirectLink&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Book your hotel room now!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Please note that this rate is guaranteed only through March 15, 2024; the price will increase after that date.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
